ブロック発動だ
人の目もクソもない
Activate it! Activate the block!
I don't care who's watching! Bury him!
潰すんだ 奴を
ブロック発動
The block is activated! Does Kaiji have any chance
なりふり構わぬ手段を
取ってきた一条に
打つ手はあるのか カイジ
now that Ichijou casts off the illusion of a fair game!?
What are you gonna do, Kaiji?
どうする カイジ
カイジ　絶体絶命
Kaiji is cornered!
１玉たりとも通さぬ非情な門番
The stern guards turn away every ball he shoots!
右打ちも不可能
Bouncing off the right is impossible!
クルーンへの道は
すべて閉ざされた
All of the paths to the trays have been closed!
Fruitless Achievement
They're completely sealed!
完全封鎖
カイジ　最初の1000万を
打ち尽くす　溶かす
Kaiji's first ten million has been blown! It's melted away!
ハハハ
どうも流れが悪いようですね
It seems like you're not doing so well.
せっかく意気込んで
来店してくださったのに
Such a pity, you seemed so excited when you arrived.
さすがに手じまいですかね
残念です
I suppose this is goodbye, then?
何 言ってる
ん？
What are you talking about?
続行だ
I'm not stopping.
Gimme another.
追加 もう１枚
え？
Another card. Hurry it up.
もう１枚だ　早くしろ
Boss?
店長
ん…
換えてやれ
あ…
Do it.
では
Of course.
What's his plan?
どういうつもりだ
さあ いくぜ
Let's go.
右打ちなんてしねえ
あくまで中央
I'm not even gonna shooting to the right. I'm going straight down the middle.
中央から強行突破だ
I'm gonna break though by force!
なんで無駄なことするんだ
Why is he wasting his balls like this!?
あのパクパクがインチキで
はじくって分かってるのに
He should know those flippers are rigged!
おかしくなったんじゃねえか
Something's not right here.
I don't get it.
どう考えたっておかしいよ
客たちの言うとおりだ
The customers are right.
なぜ こんな不毛なことを続ける
Why is he wasting his money with this?
What is he planning?
何を企んでる
This is just cruel.
ひでえな しかし
う…
I know it's supposed to be rigged, but this is pushing it.
締めるっていっても限度があるぜ
You can't just block it off completely.
ただの１発も通さねえなんて
許されるのか こんなインチキ
This is really taking it too far.
ひでえ　めちゃくちゃだ
店長
This is bullshit!
Boss!
That's it. He thinks I'll have to remove the block due to the audience reaction.
これか
この見物人の空気に負けて
俺がブロックを
解除せざるを得なくなる
He thinks I'll fall for that?
そう踏んでいるのか
He thinks I'll change it back to the normal 1/3 odds?
このまま続けていれば
いつか戻すだろう
通常の３分の１の確率に
Is that a guess?
そういう読み 計算か
Or a calculation?
フン　バカが　緩めるものか
Whatever! I'm not going to waver!
お前はこのまま死ぬ 不毛に
You're going to die a pointless death!
Pointless! Pointless! Pointless! Pointless!
不毛に　不毛に　不毛に　不毛に
不毛に死ね
Die for no reason at all!
Kaiji...
カイジ君
I'm lucky he's doing this in the morning.
助かったぜ 今が昼のさなかで
There are three times as many people here at night.
夜に比べてギャラリーも
３分の１程度
これなら問題はない
These few shouldn't cause any problems, no matter how ruthless we are.
こちらがむごく勝っても
店長 あちらの方々がお話があると
ん？
Boss!
You have a call.
カイジを確保するために
本部から派遣された方々とか
It's the group sent from HQ to retrieve Kaiji.
そうか　奴のタイムリミットは
４時だったな
I see.
His time's up at 4, isn't it?
ご苦労さまです
いえ
Excellent work.
Don't mention it.
You don't need to worry. As soon as we barricade the doors, he has no escape.
問題ありませんよ
ドアさえ固めれば奴は袋のネズミ
もし暴れるようでしたら
私どもも手伝います
If he causes any trouble, I'd be glad to help.
その点はご心配なく
That won't be necessary. But we do have an order from HQ for you.
それよりも本部から
要請がありまして
From HQ?
本部から？
はい
Yes.
このフロアに仕掛けられた
複数のカメラ
They want to use footage from the security cameras
それらで撮影している映像
to broadcast Kaiji's last game live.
カイジの勝負をライブ中継として
送信しろとのことです
ライブで？一体どこへです？
Live? Broadcast where?
地下
地下？
Underground.
Underground?
The audience will be Teiai's underground forced labor camp.
送信先は
帝愛熔工 地下強制労働施設
Take a short break!
一時 休憩とする
休憩？
A break?
昼休みには まだ早いぞ
It's too early for lunch.
あと５時間だぜ
Five hours left.
In five hours, just five hours, we find out whether Kaiji pulled it off.
あと５時間で… あと５時間で
カイジさんの成否が決まる
言うなって
だってよ
Don't even say it!
But if he didn't, we're all—
それはつまり その… 俺たちの
分かってんだよ そんなことは
You think I don't know that!?
でも言ったって
どうなるもんでもないし
But talking about it isn't going to help anything!
第一 考え出したら
苦しくなるだろ 息が
Just mentioning it makes it hurt to even breathe!
たださえ息が上がってるのに
ますます…
My chest just keeps getting tighter and tighter...
三好　大丈夫か
Miyoshi!
Are you okay!?
—What's wrong!? Are you okay!?
—Miyoshi! Miyoshi!
三好 三好 しっかりしろ　おい
Get a hold of yourself!
Hey!
苦しい
It hurts...
不安で押し潰されそうだ
The anxiety is killing me...
悪かった　俺が悪かった
I'm sorry! It's my fault!
Kaiji... Kaiji...
カイジさん　カイジさん
Kaiji!
カイジさん
助けて
Save us!
Here we go.
入りました
ＡＢＣ　３カメラ正常です
Cameras A, B, and C are working fine.
ＤＥＦ　すべて切り替わりました
We can switch through D, E, and F fine too.
あ？おお 懐かしい懐かしい
Oh, I remember doing this!
わしもやったぞ これ
This is the one I hit the 3-billion jackpot on!
何せ30億という
大当たりだったからのう
皆 驚愕放心　びっくりしてのう
エヘヘヘ
Everyone was so shocked!
さあ みんなも飲んで飲んで
遠慮せず
Drink up, men!
We're comrades! Brothers!
我らは同じ同胞　兄弟だ
Yes, sir...
制裁
あっ
Punish him.
やる気なく｢はあ｣と言った貴様
Punish him for that listless "yes, sir!"
制裁
あ…
Sir, I didn't mean to—
いや あの 私は別に
兄弟とはいえ序列はあるのだ
圧倒的に
There is an order among brothers! An inviolable order!
あ… いや その
会長　すみません
I'm sorry, Sir! I really didn't mean to offend you!
私はそんなつもりでは
会長　会長
アハハ　さあ 飲んで飲んで
Now drink! Drink!
はい！いただきます
Yes, sir! Thank you, sir!
アハハ
ええな ええな アハハ
Excellent!
Kaiji! This is Kaiji!
カイジ君　カイジ君じゃ
He still hasn't learned his lesson!
やっとるのう
相変わらずバカなことを
皆の衆　よく見ておけ
Take a close look, gentlemen!
He's got more guts than it looks like.
この男 こう見えて
なかなかの つわものでのう
And here he is risking his life on the outside in his last gamble.
このつわものがシャバでの存命
己の人生を懸けて
最後の大勝負
この土壇場 どうジタバタするのか
It's his final moments.
Watch how he struggles.
それをよく見ておくのだ
後学のために　な？
You may need the example someday.
は… はい
Yes, sir!
ハハハ　壊れてる壊れてる
He's crumbling, he's crumbling!
なぜ するのかのう
Why does he do this?
This ruinous, murderous, self-destructive gambling?
破滅 死滅 自滅覚悟の愚行を
ギャンブルを
ウヒヒ…
フン
なぜ どうして
無駄なことを続ける
Why?
Why does he continue his fruitless battle?
見物人たちの あきれにも似た感情
The audience seem to have given up!
ここが正念場だ
It's do or die.
待つしかない
All we can do is wait and endure.
今は ただ耐え
ノックし続けるしかない
All we can do is keep knocking!
Keep knocking on the door of high-stakes gambling, hoping Lady Luck will open up.
この一か八かの博打を
勝利へと導く運命のドア
We can't open the door. All we can do is wait for it to open.
こちらからは開けない
そのドアが開くまで ただ待つ
ノックの手を休めず
We can't stop until we're physically incapable.
もしノックが実らず
ドアが開かなければ それまで
それが俺と奴の天運 宿運
This is our fate, our destiny.
賭けは散り 沈む
We lose, and fall...
沈まざるを得ない
王国という あの地獄へ
We can do nothing but fall.
Fall down into that abyss.
It's do or die, Kaiji!
ここが正念場だ カイジ
カイジさん
今頃どうしてるんだろう
I wonder what Kaiji's doing right now?
He probably just took the money and decided to go out with a bang.
とっくに金はスッちゃって
ただ漫然と残り時間を
過ごしているのかな
We haven't heard from him in so long. That's probably what he did.
ずっと音沙汰なしなんだから
その可能性が一番高いけど
ハア
でもカイジさんなら
もしかして… もしかして
But what if? What if Kaiji...
Early lunch today.
少し早いが昼飯を配っておく
ん？
何だ？
Huh?
本来 休憩時間中に
テレビを鑑賞するなど
Usually, watching television on break is forbidden underground.
この地下では許されない
あり得ないシャバっ気
An impossible luxury for the denizens of hell!
ざわつく地獄の住人たち
Today, President Hyodo will visit this facility.
今日はたまたま この施設に
兵藤会長がお見えになっている
The President is giving you this special opportunity to watch TV.
その会長のご厚意で特別に
テレビ中継を見ることが許された
We'll be showing a live broadcast that's very important to a few of you.
この中の何人かにとっては
非常に興味深い中継となるだろう
Live?
中継？
サッカーか野球か
Soccer? Baseball, maybe?
フフ　覚えている者も多いはずだ
Most of you should remember the man who left on furlough three weeks ago.
３週間ほど前 この施設から
一時外出した男のことを
え？
カイジさん
What!?
Kaiji!
お…
おい あいつか
It's him?
あの大槻を倒したとかっていう
The man who took down Ohtsuki?
Where is he?
あいつがどうかしたのか
Right now, he's gambling in a Teiai casino.
その男が今 我が帝愛グループの
経営するカジノで勝負をしている
カイジさんが？
勝負を？
Kaiji's—
—Gambling!?
むろん 彼自身と ここにいる
何人かの解放をかけてだ
He's betting his own release, and some of yours as well.
えー
マジですか それ
Really!?
自分の目で確かめてみろ
See for yourself.
Here he is.
映ります
あ… あ… マジかよ
Is this really happening!?
Kaiji! Kaiji!
カイジさん
カイジ君
カ… カイジさん
Kaiji's risking it all for us...
カイジさんが
俺たちのために勝負を
Wait, he's playing pachinko!?
ちょっと待て　カイジさんが
やってるこれって… パチンコ？
カ… カイジさん
Kaiji...
何だよ
What the hell!? We put up more than 60 million!
俺たちの借金は全部で
6000万を超えるんだぜ
今更 パチンコなんかして
どうするんだよ
What the hell is he playing Pachinko for!?
どういうことなんだ カイジさん
前田さん　落ち着けって
—What's going on!?
—Calm down, Maeda!
He's right, though.
でも前田さんの言うとおりだよ
パチンコなんかで
俺たちの借金分を稼ぐなんて
Pachinko will never pay out enough.
そんなこと無理な話だ
He may as well not bother.
そうでもない
え？
That's not true.
This machine uses 4,000-yen balls.
この台は１玉4000円
4,000!?
4000円？
普通の1000倍だ
That's a thousand times more than normal!
限りなくゼロに近い確率だが
今 万が一当たれば
It's almost impossible, but if he wins he'll have six or seven hundred million.
６億から７億
な… ７億？
Seven hundred million!?
え？
マジかよ
Really!?
何だ それ
７億
What the...
700 million...
聞いたことねえぞ そんなパチンコ
I've never heard of pachinko with those stakes!
700 million what? 700 million perica?
７億って７億ペリカか？
バカ野郎　円に決まってるだろ
No way! It's gotta be yen!
Freedom...
解放
ああ
Yeah! If Kaiji hits the jackpot, we're all free!
出れば間違いなく
俺たち全員 解放だ
カイジさん
カイジ君
Kaiji!
カイジさん
If each ball is 4,000 yen, and Kaiji left with 800,000....
１玉4000円ってことは
カイジさんは80万持ってるから
何発だ？
How many shots is that?
ハハハ　80万などという はした金
あの台じゃ２分で溶けるぞ
You can easily lose 800,000 on that machine in two minutes.
え？
それじゃあ…
Then...
It looks like he came with 50 million.
奴は元手として5000万という
金を用意してきたそうだ
5000万？
50 million!?
どうやって そんな大金を？
How did he get that much money!?
当然 高利の借金だろ
He borrowed it from a loan shark, of course.
カイジさん… あっ
Kaiji...
At that moment, Kaiji's second Paqy card ran out—he's shot 20 million yen!
この時 カイジ　２枚目のパッキー
すなわち2000万を打ち尽くす
お…
追加だ
Gimme another.
カイジ
迷わず３枚目のパッキーを購入
Unhesitatingly, Kaiji buys his third Paqy card!
あれでパッキーは３枚目
That's his third Paqy card.
He's reaching the midpoint of his attempt.
勝負は もう中盤
そろそろ焦りが出てくる頃だ
Soon, he'll get nervous.
Nervous?
焦り？
当然だ
Of course. If he doesn't win he gets sent back here.
このまま当たりが来ずに終われば
ここに逆戻り
If that happens, it will take him more than a century to repay the money he's borrowed.
そうなった場合 上乗せになった
借金から換算して
奴の終了年数は軽く100年を超える
え？
100？
A hundred...
A hundred years!?
100年？
He'll be trapped here forever.
つまり ここの住人だ
For his whole life. Just like you.
生涯　お前たちもな
生涯 住人
それはある意味 死より恐ろしい刑
The rest of one's life in the abyss!
A fate more fearsome than death!
最悪の宣告
The ultimate punishment!
カイジさん　頑張れ
Don't give up, Kaiji!
そうだ カイジさん
カイジさん
Yeah, Kaiji!
Kaiji!
頑張れ カイジさん
頑張れ
Keep trying, Kaiji!
You can do it!
You can do it, Kaiji!
頑張れ
カイジさん
勝て　勝って抜けよう
この地獄を一緒に
Win... Win, and let's escape this hell...
Go for it, Kaiji!
カイジさん　いけ　いけ
Go!
いけ！
いけ カイジさん
いけ カイジさん！
Go for it, Kaiji!
エヘヘ
See how pitiful those worms are!
醜く わめいておるのう
地下の虫どもが
のう？
はい
I can hardly bear to watch.
見苦しい 見苦しい
まったく なんてぶざまな姿だ
They're pathetic.
アハハハ　分かるか お前たち
は？
You understand why I'm allowing them a television now, right?
なぜ わしがあの地下のクズどもに
テレビを見せることを許したか
え？い… いや
Well...
そ… それはその
いや その何というか…
It's, uh, how shall I put it...
す… すいません
アハハハ
I'm sorry!
無力
は？
Powerlessness.
To show you how powerless they are.
無力であることを
知ってもらうためじゃ
祈り 応援 そんなものの無力
Their prayers, their cheers, these do nothing.
I want you to know just how weak they are.
いかに効力がないかを
お前らに知ってもらいたいのじゃ
They're nothing but the superstitions of scum like that.
あんなものはクズどもの気休め
浅はかな迷信よ
逆に言うなら
If you ever reach the point where you need to pray, you're already a failure of a man.
祈るようになったら
人間も終わりという話だ
ハハハ　出んじゃろう
あの沼は出ん
It won't pay.
The Bog won't pay.
あれはクズどものヒーローに
出せる台ではない
It won't pay to their hero. They're wasting their time.
所詮 無理な話だ
That machine pays only to men who are already made!
あれは功成り名を遂げた者だけが
出せる名機
Not just to anyone!
誰でもというわけにはいかぬ
ハハハ　コケか真か
Truth or lie?
その人間の持つ運 才能 性質 器量
A man's luck, his talent, his nature, his talent... All these make him a man!
すなわち人間の器
And the Bog judges them all!
まさにその器を測る台
Sadly for Kaiji, it will find him lacking.
残念じゃが
力不足じゃろう カイジ君では
Kaiji!
カイジさん
頑張れ
Don't give up!
Their path is closed.
当然 こいつらの道 未来も
閉ざされる
人頼み 神頼みで声援を送れば
These pitiful fools have no future if they cast their lot in with other men, or with God.
祈りが通じると思っている
哀れなクズどもの未来がな
Worms like these don't even have the right to dream!
そもそも地下に落ちた虫けらに
未来を夢見る資格などない
ない　ない
They don't!
カイジさん　カイジさん…
Kaiji! Kaiji!
４５組の熱狂とは対照的に
In contrast to the 45s' burning passion, a chill envelops the spectators at the casino!
沼を囲む見物人たちの間には
次第に しらけた空気
空しさ 虚脱感が漂い始める
They begin to give up, become despondent!
Pointless acts! Fruitless effort! Foolishness!
意味のない行為 実らぬ努力
まさに愚行
They see Kaiji's determination as nothing but foolishness!
彼らにはカイジの執着が
まさに愚行にしか見えない
あーあ
The audience begins to leave!
ついに その場を
離れ始めるギャラリー
One, two, three!
１人　２人　３人
気がつけばカイジの周りには
When Kaiji looks up, he sees only Endoh, Sakazaki, and an audience of three!
坂崎 遠藤らの他には
わずか３人のギャラリー
The only others left are the casino staff and Ichijou!
そして 店の従業員と一条が
残るのみ
But Kaiji continues to play!
しかしカイジ 打ち続ける
３枚目のパッキーも残り500万
5 million remain on his third Paqy card!
The Bog has swallowed half his stack—a whole 25 million!
既に軍資金の半分2500万が
沼にのみ込まれた
だがしかし つぎ込む
ひたすら つぎ込み続ける
But! But! He keeps shooting! Keeps shooting the 4,000-yen balls!
１発4000円の玉
It does not open! It will not open!
開かない　開かない
開かない
It will not open!
All he can do is pound on the unyielding door!
微動だにしない その扉
そこに打つ　打つ
打ち続ける
Can this wasteful act bring him victory!?
この一見 不毛な行為に
勝算はあるのか
カイジに残された
シャバでの猶予は あと４時間
Kaiji has only four hours left outside!
240分を切る
The 240 minute mark passes!
カイジ 間に合うのか　カイジ
Will Kaiji make it in time!?
Kaiji!
Kaiji gets a second game!
First, the Kaiji anime has become a Mobage online game!
The player and Kaiji become the ultimate gamblers by winning those cruel games!
Kaiji's bets... The Bog, Chinchirorin, E-card, and more... are playable on PC!
It's called Teiai Casino!
Its atmosphere is overwhelming!